Welcome to a really exciting module. In this module
we're going to be building a chat app. And not only is it going to look beautiful, but it's also going
to be super powerful because we're going to power our messenger using Firebase Firestore. And this is
what I'll look like by the time we're done.
So it's got some beautiful animations and we're gonna be looking at how to implement animations in
Flutter but also we're going to be creating this beautiful messenger user interface and we're going
to be able to set up a group chat and we're also going to implement authentication and registration
so the users will be able to register and log in so that they can chat with other users. First things
first.
As always we're going to head over to the GitHub Repository for flash chats and we're going to clone
that repository into our local system.
So we're going to check out project from version control and we're gonna go ahead and clone this project.
And once it's done, it will open it up and get our dependencies.
So if you take a look inside our lib folder, you'll see that we have a whole bunch of screens so let's
open all of them up.
We've got our welcome screen, our log in and registration screens and finally we've got our chat screen where
the chats are going to actually happen. Once you already and setup, head over to the next lesson where
we're going to get started building out our Flash Chat app.